For some, 13 feels like it was just yesterday. For Jenna, it was.
13 Going on 30 is a comedy, fantasy, romance film directed by Gary Winick.
After total humiliation at her thirteenth birthday party,
Jenna Rink wants to just hide until she's thirty.
Thanks to some magic wishing dust, Jenna's prayer has been answered.
With a knockout body, a fabulous wardrobe, an athlete boyfriend, a dream
job, and superstar friends, this can't be a better life.
But soon Jenna realizes that adult life isn’t as easy as she hoped for.
Jenna Rink, played by Jennifer Garner.
Matt Flamhaff, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Lucy Wyman, played by Judy Greer.
Richard Kneeland, played by Andy Serkis.
Bev Rink, played by Kathy Baker.
Wayne Rink, played by Phil Reeves.
13 Going on 30 (released as Suddenly 30 in some countries) is a 2004 American fantasy romantic comedy film written by Cathy Yuspa and Josh
Goldsmith, directed by Gary Winick, starring Jennifer Garner and Mark Ruffalo, and produced by Susan Arnold and Donna Arkoff Roth.
The film is about a 13-year-old girl in 1987 who awakens to find herself
suddenly 30 years old and living in 2004 as a fashion editor.
13 Going on 30 received generally positive reviews from critics, with many
praising Garner's performance and its nostalgic environment.
It was also praised for its humorous plot and self-empowering message.
The film was also a commercial success, earning $22 million in its first week
and becoming one of the year's biggest-selling DVD rental titles.
Its total box office profit was over $96 million.
Additionally, the soundtrack charted inside the top
50 on the US Billboard 200 chart.
Garner's acting earned her nominations from both the MTV
Movie Awards and the Teen Choice Awards.
The film explores themes of new york city,
photographer, editor-in-chief, time travel, wish.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.